{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Huì",
      "answer": "会"
    },
    {
      "question": "Diǎnr",
      "answer": "点儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sījī",
      "answer": "司机"
    },
    {
      "question": "Diǎn zhōng",
      "answer": "点钟"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chà",
      "answer": "差"
    },
    {
      "question": "Huí",
      "answer": "回"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shàngkè",
      "answer": "上课"
    },
    {
      "question": "Néng",
      "answer": "能"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dào",
      "answer": "到"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiào",
      "answer": "教"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīngyǔ",
      "answer": "英语"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sūnnǚr",
      "answer": "孙女儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Suìshu",
      "answer": "岁数"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shù",
      "answer": "数"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hái",
      "answer": "还"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fēnzhōng",
      "answer": "分钟"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bàibài",
      "answer": "拜拜"
    }


  ]
}
